RG 005:035, Office of the Governor: Thomas J. Meskill (1971-1975)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Subject File, 1971-1975
  - Education – Reference Materials (Box A-630)
  - Education – Speaking Engagements (Box A-630)
  - Elderly (Box A-630)
  - Election 1972 (Box A-630)
  - Election 1976 (Box A-630)
  - Elections (5 folders) (Box A-630)
  - Elections (Box A-630)
    - Absentee Voting (Box A-630)
    - Commission (Box A-630)
    - Committee (Box A-630)
    - 1974 Election Information (Box A-630)
    - Reference Materials (Box A-630)
  - Elections – Republican Election, 1971 Fall (Box A-631)
  - Electrical Examining Board (Box A-631)
  - Electrical Examining Board – Stanley Page’s File (Box A-631)
  - Electrical Work Examining Board (Box A-631)
  - Embalmers and Funeral Directors (Box A-631)
  - Employee Selection Procedures (Box A-631)
  - Employees Association (Box A-631)
  - Employees (Box A-631)
    - Disability Retirement (Box A-631)
    - Letters of Endorsement (Box A-631)
    - Retirement Commission (Box A-631)
    - State (Box A-631)
    - State – Retirement, 5 folders (Box A-631)
    - Suggestion Awards Board (Box A-631)
    - Suggestion Program (Box A-631)
  - Employment – National Employment Association (Box A-631)
  - Endorsements (Box A-631)
  - Energy Advisory Board (Box A-632)
  - Energy (Box A-632)
    - Agenda Utility Companies/State Emergency Officials Meeting, 1973 December 19 (Box A-632)
    - Children’s Letter (Box A-632)
    - Connecticut Energy Board (Box A-632)
    - Conservation (Box A-632)
    - Conservation Letter (Holiday Closing), 1973 December 4 (Box A-632)
    - Correspondence A-E, 13 folders (Box A-632)
  - Energy: (Box A-633)
    - Correspondence F-N, 13 folders (Box A-633)
  - Energy (Box A-634)
    - Correspondence O-Z, 9 folders (Box A-634)
  - Energy Crisis (Box A-635)
    - Information, 3 folders (Box A-635)
    - Letters to TV Stations (Box A-635)
    - Liquid Gas (Box A-635)
    - Statement by Atty. General of Mass. (Box A-635)
    - Telegram to Federal Power Com./Liquid Gas (Box A-635)
  - Energy (Box A-635)
    - “Dear Commissioners” Ex. Order No. 21 (Box A-635)
    - Dear Concerned (Box A-635)
    - Emergency Energy Agency, 3 folders (Box A-635)
    - Emergency Energy Agency/Legislation (Box A-635)
    - Emergency Energy Agency Press Releases (Box A-635)
    - Federal Energy Office (Box A-635)
    - Gas Rationing (Box A-635)
  - Energy (Box A-636)
    - Gasland Letter (Box A-636)
    - Gasoline Shortage (Box A-636)
    - Gasoline Shortage, 1974 February 1 (Box A-636)
    - Governor’s Summertime Energy Program (Box A-636)
    - Highway Lighting (Box A-636)
    - Ice Storm (Box A-636)
    - Ideas (Box A-636)
    - Legislation (Box A-636)
    - Letter – Executive Order 21 (Box A-636)
    - Meeting for First Selectman, 1973 November 26 (Box A-636)
    - Meeting, 1973 December 20 (Box A-636)
    - Message (Box A-636)
    - Municipal Energy Coordinators (Box A-636)
    - NEPEX (Box A-636)
    - National Energy Plan (Box A-636)
    - New Energy Alert 24 (Box A-636)
    - Northeast Utilities Weekly (Box A-636)
    - Planning – Governor’s Conference Room, 1973 December 20 (Box A-636)
    - Policy (Box A-636)
    - Policy Booklet (Box A-636)
    - Policy Shortage (NERC Resolution) (Box A-636)
    - Policy Statement (Box A-636)
    - Printed Letter Sent in Response to Pledge Card (Box A-636)
    - School Closing (Box A-636)
    - Speech Outlines (Box A-636)
    - Task Force (Box A-636)
  - Engineers (Box A-636)
  - Environmental Arts and Crafts Council (Box A-636)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (Box A-636)
  - Equal Rights (Box A-636)
  - Equal Opportunity (Box A-636)
  - Equine Commission (Box A-636)
  - Equipment, 2 folders (Box A-636)
  - Equipment – Stanley Page’s files (Box A-636)
  - Etherington Commission – See Services & Expenditures Commission (Box A-636)
  - Ethics (Box A-636)
  - Ethnic Groups (Box A-636)
  - Examining Boards (Box A-636)
  - Executive Order (Box A-636)
  - Executive Order 23 (Comprehensive Training) (Box A-636)
  - Executive Papers (Box A-636)
  - Executive Reorganization (Box A-636)
  - Extradition (Box A-636)
  - Fact Sheets (Box A-637)
  - Family Planning (Box A-637)
  - Family Relations (Box A-637)
  - Favorable Letters (Box A-637)
  - Federal (Box A-637)
  - Federal Appointments (Box A-637)
  - Federal Budget (Box A-637)
  - Federal Census (Box A-637)
  - Federal Executive Board (Box A-637)
  - Federal Government (Box A-637)
  - Federal Grant Award Notification & Dissemination (Box A-637)
  - Federal – ICC (Box A-637)
  - Federal Income Tax (Box A-637)
  - Federal Legislation (Box A-637)
  - Federal Legislation – Meeting with Congressional Delegation, 1973 August 20 (Box A-637)
  - Federal Legislation – 93rd Congress (Box A-637)
  - Federal Regional Intergov. Conference, 1972 June (Box A-637)
  - Federal Regional Council – June 24th (Box A-637)
  - Federal Regional Council – Minutes of Meeting in Hartford -, 1971 March (Box A-637)
  - Federal Regional Council – Minutes of Meetings (Box A-637)
  - Federal Regional Council of New England, 2 folders (Box A-637)
  - Federal – State, 2 folders (Box A-637)
  - Federal – State, 2 folders (Box A-638)
  - Federal – State (Box A-638)
    - A-95 (Box A-638)
    - ACIR (Advisory Comm. On Intergovernmental Relations) (Box A-638)
    - Aging (Box A-638)
    - Agriculture (Box A-638)
    - Alcoholism (Box A-638)
    - Children & Youth (Box A-638)
    - Clearinghouse (Box A-638)
    - Community Affairs (Box A-638)
    - Consumer Protection (Box A-638)
    - Corrections (Box A-638)
    - Criminal Adm., Planning Committee (Box A-638)
    - Development Comm. (Box A-638)
    - Education (Box A-638)
    - Environmental Project (Box A-638)
    - Health (Box A-638)
    - Higher Education (Box A-638)
    - Historical Comm. (Box A-638)
    - Insurance (Box A-638)
    - Integrated Grant Administration Program (Box A-638)
    - Labor (Box A-638)
    - Library (Box A-638)
    - Mental Health (Box A-638)
    - Motor Vehicle (Box A-638)
    - Personnel (Box A-638)
    - Public Works (Box A-638)
    - Reg. Bilingual Info. Center (Box A-638)
    - Revenue Sharing (Box A-638)
    - Rural Development (Box A-638)
    - State Police (Box A-638)
    - Tax Department (Box A-638)
    - Transportation (Box A-638)
    - Treasurer’s Office (Box A-638)
    - Univ. of Connecticut (Box A-638)
    - Welfare (Box A-638)
  - Federal Technical Assistance Program (Box A-638)
  - Field Services Bureau (Box A-638)
  - Finance (Box A-638)
  - Finance Advisory Committee (Box A-638)
  - Finance Advisory Committee – Audit Report (Box A-638)
  - Finance & Control, 2 folders (Box A-638)
  - Finance & Control, 6 folders (Box A-639)
  - Finance & Control (Box A-639)
    - Allotments Log, 1970 April - 1972 June (Box A-639)
    - Barry Budlong’s Schedule (Box A-639)
    - Central Collections (Box A-639)
    - Central Collections Audit Report (Box A-639)
    - Contingency Finance (Box A-639)
  - Finance & Control: Purchasing Division Audit (Box A-639)
  - Fire Administration (Box A-639)
  - Fire Fighting Commission (Box A-639)
  - Fire Marshall (Box A-639)
  - Fire Service Coordination Committee (Box A-639)
  - Firearms – Registration (Box A-640)
  - Firearms Association – Connecticut (Box A-640)
  - Fiscal Policy – History (Box A-640)
  - Flag Rules (Box A-640)
  - Flying Feds Report (Box A-640)
  - Food Prices (Box A-640)
  - Foreign & Interstate Commerce (Box A-640)
  - Foreign Affairs & Aid (Box A-640)
  - Foreign Trade (Box A-640)
  - Fourth of July (Box A-640)
  - Francophone Cultural Commission (Box A-640)
  - Freund (General) (Box A-640)
  - Fuel Allocation (Box A-640)
  - Fuel Shortage (Box A-640)
  - Fund Freeze – Job Freeze (Box A-640)
  - Fund Raising (Box A-640)
  - Gasoline Exemption Bill (Box A-640)
  - Gasoline Phone In (Box A-640)
  - Gasoline Price Increase, 4 folders (Box A-640)
  - Gasoline Shortage (Box A-641)
  - Gasoline Stations Abandoned (Box A-641)
  - Gasoline Station Closings (Box A-641)
  - Gasoline Tax Exemption Letter (Box A-641)
  - General (Box A-641)
  - General Accounting Office (Box A-641)
  - General Assembly/Special Session, 1974 (Box A-641)
  - General Services Administration (Box A-641)
  - Gentile (Box A-641)
  - Geological Survey (Box A-641)
  - Get Well Wishes (Box A-641)
  - Goldwater – Roaney Amendment (Box A-641)
  - “Good” Letters (Box A-641)
  - Government Economy (Box A-641)
  - Government Efficiency (Box A-641)
  - Government Reorganization (State) (Box A-641)
  - Government Spending (Box A-641)
  - Gov. Meskill – Personal (Box A-641)
  - Governor’s (Box A-641)
    - Campaign (Offers of Assistance) (Box A-641)
    - Duties (Box A-641)
    - Opinion (Box A-641)
    - Pension (Box A-641)
    - Personal Security Force (Box A-641)
    - Portrait (Box A-641)
    - Programs: Info. Mgt. Task Force (Box A-641)
  - Grant, Dr. (Box A-641)
  - Grants/Federal (Box A-641)
  - Grants to Towns (Box A-641)
  - Grasso (Box A-641)
  - Greater Hartford Community Council (Box A-641)
  - Greater Hartford Open (Box A-641)
  - Greater Hartford Process, 2 folders (Box A-641)
  - Greater Hartford Process – Drafts (Box A-641)
  - Greek Independence Medal (Box A-641)
  - Greetings (Box A-641)
  - Grievance Committee (Box A-641)
  - Gun Control (Box A-641)
  - Harambee (Box A-641)
  - Harbormasters (Box A-641)
  - Hartell, Lee R. – Resolution (Box A-641)
  - Hartford (Box A-641)
  - Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box A-641)
  - Hartford Juvenile Court & Detention Home (Box A-641)
  - Hawaiian Room (Box A-641)
  - Health, Education & Welfare/ABCD #H-0441 (Box A-642)
  - Health, Education & Welfare Grant H-1083 WACAB (Box A-642)
  - Health, Education & Welfare: Health Services Legislation (Box A-642)
  - Heating & Piping Board (Box A-642)
  - Hellier (Box A-642)
  - Historical – Noah Webster Foundation (Box A-642)
  - Historical Commission, 5 folders (Box A-642)
    - Audit Report (Box A-642)
    - Film (Box A-642)
  - Historical Commission (Box A-643)
    - Interest Group Lists (Box A-643)
    - Museum, 2 folders (Box A-643)
  - Historical Societies Budget (Box A-643)
  - Holy Land – Catacombs (Box A-643)
  - Homeopathic Exam. Board (Box A-643)
  - Honorary Chairmanship, 2 folders (Box A-643)
  - Hospital Costs, 4 folders (Box A-643)
  - Hot Dogs (Box A-643)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 3 folders (Box A-643)
  - Human Resource (Box A-644)
  - Human Rights Commission, 8 folders (Box A-644)
  - Human Services, 3 folders (Box A-644)
  - Human Services, Council (Box A-644)
  - Humane Society (Box A-644)
  - Humanities Council (Box A-644)
  - Hunting (Box A-645)
  - Huntington Historical Society (Box A-645)
  - Hypertricholigists (Box A-645)
  - IBM (Box A-645)
  - Ice Storm (Box A-645)
  - Impeachment (Box A-645)
  - Imports (Box A-645)
  - Inaugural Ball (Box A-645)
  - Inauguration, 1972 (Box A-645)
  - Independence Day – July 4 (Box A-645)
  - Independence Day re: Bell Ringing And Hall of Flags (Box A-645)
  - Industrial Modernization Committee (Box A-645)
  - Inflation (Box A-645)
  - Inflation Fact Sheet (Box A-645)
  - Information Bureau, Governor’s State, 4 folders (Box A-645)
  - Information Bureau, Governor’s State, 2 folders (Box A-646)
    - Civic Organizations (Box A-646)
    - Correspondence (Box A-646)
    - Fire Chiefs (Box A-646)
    - 7-Jan-74 (Box A-646)
    - 21-Jan-74 (Box A-646)
    - Letter Sent to Banks (Box A-646)
    - Letters to Police Chiefs (Box A-646)
    - Photographs (Box A-646)
    - (Pins) Jan. 10, 1974 President of Public, Private (Box A-646)
    - Parochial Higher Education Facility (Box A-646)
    - (Pins) Letters to Insurance Companies on Info Pins (Box A-646)
  - Information Management Task Force (Box A-646)
  - Integrated Grant Adm. Program (IGA) (Box A-646)
  - Interand Corporation (Box A-646)
  - Interfaith Commission (Box A-646)
  - “Intergov” (ACIR) Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 2 folders (Box A-646)
  - Intergovernmental Cooperation (Box A-646)
  - Intergovernmental Personnel Act (1970), 2 folders (Box A-646)
  - Intergovernmental Personnel Act (1970), 2 folders (Box A-647)
  - Intergovernmental Personnel Act – Grants, 2 folders (Box A-647)
  - Intergovernmental Relations Comm. (Boston Federal Executive Board) (Box A-647)
  - Interior Dept. – Milford Lab (Box A-647)
  - Interior, Department of the (Box A-647)
  - Internal Revenue Service (Box A-647)
  - International Issues (Box A-647)
  - Interns (Box A-647)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 2 folders (Box A-647)
  - Interstate Sanitation Commission (Box A-647)
  - Introduction, Letter of (Box A-647)
  - Inventor’s Day (Box A-647)
  - Investment Advisory Council (Box A-647)
  - Ireland (Box A-647)
  - Irish No. A.C. (Northern Aid Committee) (Box A-647)
  - Israeli Arab War (Box A-647)
  - Issues (Box A-647)
  - Issues: Federal (Box A-647)
  - Judicial, 6 folders (Box A-648)
  - Judicial – Admin. Procedures Act (Box A-648)
  - Judicial – Audit 18th Circuit Court at Winsted (Box A-648)
  - Judicial Department (Box A-648)
  - Judicial Review Council (Box A-648)
  - Judiciary (Box A-648)
  - Junk Mail (Box A-648)
  - Jury (Box A-648)
  - Justice, Department of – FBI (Box A-648)
  - Keepsakes (Box A-649)
  - Killian (Box A-649)
  - King, Martin L. (Box A-649)
  - Knights of St. Patrick (Box A-649)
  - Kozlowski (Box A-649)
  - Landscape Architects (Box A-649)
  - Law Enforcement, 3 folders (Box A-649)
  - Law Enforcement Asst. (Box A-649)
  - Law Enforcement: Planning Comm. on Criminal Administration (Box A-649)
  - Law Revision Commission (Box A-649)
  - Laws (Box A-649)
  - League of Women Voters (Box A-649)
  - Legacy of Parks (Box A-649)
  - Legal Aid (Gordon Allen) (Box A-649)
  - Legal Assistance – New Haven Legal Assistance Association, Inc. – VISTA (Box A-649)
  - Legal Holidays (Box A-649)
  - Legal Matters, 2 folders (Box A-649)
  - Legal Publication (Box A-649)
  - Legal Services (Box A-649)
  - Legal Services (Box A-650)
  - Legal Services Program (Box A-650)
  - Legislation (2 folders) (Box A-650)
    - Bills, 10 folders (Box A-650)
    - Federal, 2 folders (Box A-650)
    - Libraries (Box A-650)
    - 1972 (Box A-650)
    - PA-107 (Box A-650)
    - S.B. 484 (Box A-650)
    - Senate Joint Resolution 108 (Box A-650)
  - Legislative (Box A-650)
    - Audit Review Committee (Box A-650)
    - Commissioner (Box A-650)
    - Correspondence (Box A-650)
    - Digest (Box A-650)
    - Inquiry (Box A-650)
    - Management – Audit Report (Box A-650)
  - Legislative Management (Joint Committee) (Box A-651)
  - Legislative Pay Increases (Box A-651)
  - Legislative Reapportionment (Box A-651)
  - Legislature (Box A-651)
  - Legislature – Committee on Program Review and Evaluation (Box A-651)
  - Legislature, 1973 (Box A-651)
  - Legislature – Trailer Session, 1974 June 17 (Box A-651)
  - Letters to the Editor (Box A-651)
  - Libraries and Connecticut State Library Association, 3 folders (Box A-651)
  - Libraries – State Library Committee (Box A-651)
  - Licensing (Box A-651)
  - Lieutenant Governor (Box A-651)
  - Limousine (Box A-651)
  - Liquor (Box A-651)
  - Liquor Control (Box A-651)
  - Liquor – Drinking Age & Hours (Box A-651)
  - Local Government (Box A-651)
  - Marketing Authority (Box A-652)
  - Marketing Research (Box A-652)
  - Mayors (Box A-652)
  - Mayors, Connecticut Conference of (Box A-652)
  - Mayors, U.S. Conference of (Box A-652)
  - Medical Association, American (Box A-652)
  - Medical Examining Board (Box A-652)
  - Medical Service, Inc. (Box A-652)
  - Medical Society – Conn. State (Box A-652)
  - Medicare (Box A-652)
  - Medicolegal Investigation (Box A-652)
  - Memberships (Box A-652)
  - Memorandums from TJM (Box A-652)
  - Memorandums – Miscellaneous (Box A-652)
  - Memorandums to Gov. Meskill (Box A-652)
  - Memorial Day (Box A-652)
  - Message by State Governors (Box A-652)
  - Metropolitan District Commission (Box A-652)
  - Middle East Oil (Box A-652)
  - Military, 3 folders (Box A-652)
  - Military (Box A-652)
    - Air Force (Box A-652)
    - Army (Box A-652)
    - Army Corps of Engineers, 2 folders (Box A-652)
    - Coast Guard (Box A-652)
    - Constituency Mail (Box A-652)
    - Personnel (Box A-653)
    - Releases 24-28, 1973 September (Box A-653)
    - Releases 18-31, 1973 October-November (Box A-653)
    - Releases: 28, 1974 May-June (Box A-653)
    - Top Leadership (Box A-653)
    - Gen. Freund (Box A-653)
    - Governor’s Foot Guard (Box A-653)
    - Horse Guard (Box A-653)
    - Information from Walsh (Box A-653)
    - National Guard, 2 folders (Box A-653)
    - National Guard Congratulations (Box A-653)
    - Navy (Box A-653)
    - ROTC (Box A-653)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box A-653)
  - Military: Special Orders & Press Releases, 7 folders (Box A-654)
  - Military: Special Orders & Press Releases, 1 folder (Box A-655)
  - Military Staff (Box A-655)
  - Military (Box A-655)
    - U.S. Air Force Academy (Box A-655)
    - U.S. Coast Guard Academy (Box A-655)
    - U.S. Merchant Marine Academy (Box A-655)
    - West Point Academy (Box A-655)
  - Mini Bikes (Box A-655)
  - Mining (Box A-655)
  - Minorities – Communications: Spanish/Polish/Women (Box A-655)
  - Minorities – Women (Box A-655)
  - Minority Affairs Meeting (Box A-655)
  - Minority Enterprise (Box A-655)
  - Minority Groups (Box A-655)
  - Miscegenation (Box A-655)
  - Miscellaneous (Box A-655)
  - Missing in Action (Box A-655)
  - Missing Persons (Box A-655)
  - MIT Research (Box A-655)
  - Mobile Homes – Jensen’s (Box A-655)
  - Mobile Homes Parks (Box A-655)
  - Model Cities (Box A-655)
  - Model Code Laws (Box A-655)
  - Mortgage Authority, 2 folders (Box A-655)
  - Mystic Seaport (Box A-655)
  - NAACP (Box A-655)
  - NASA (Box A-655)
  - National Council of Teachers of English (Congratulations) (Box A-655)
  - National Election, 1976 (Box A-656)
  - National Science Foundation, 2 folders (Box A-656)
  - National Science Foundation – Proposed Trial R & D Program, 1971 (Box A-656)
  - Naturalized Citizens (Box A-656)
  - Naturopathic Examiners Board (Box A-656)
  - Nazi Party March, 1974 (Box A-656)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corps (Box A-656)
  - New Britain Murders (Box A-656)
  - New England Regional Commission (Box A-656)
  - New England Republican Governors’ Association (Box A-656)
  - NIKE Base – Ansonia (Box A-656)
  - Nixon – Form Letters Pro & Con (Box A-656)
  - No Address File – Letters (Box A-656)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization – NATO (Box A-656)
  - Norwich Office (Box A-656)
  - Notary (Box A-656)
  - Notary Public (Box A-656)
  - Nuclear Weapons (Box A-656)
  - Nurses, Association of & Board of Examiners for Nursing (Box A-656)
  - Nursing Home Administrators (Box A-656)
  - Occupational Licensing (Box A-657)
  - OEP – Office of Emergency Preparedness (Box A-657)
  - Office – General (Box A-657)
  - Office of Management & Budget (Box A-657)
    - A-85 (Box A-657)
    - A-95 and A-98 (Box A-657)
    - A-95 and A-98 – Quarterly Reports of Federal Grants (Box A-657)
    - Federal Grants (Box A-657)
    - Federal Task Force “Flying Feds” (Box A-657)
    - Research Material (Box A-657)
  - Official Legal Publications (Box A-657)
  - Official Legal Publications – Audit Report (Box A-657)
  - Official Statement Denials (See Also Boxes A-928,ff) (Box A-657)
  - Official Statements (See Also Boxes A-928,ff), 4 folders (Box A-657)
  - Official Statements (See Also Boxes A-928,ff), 1974 (Box A-657)
  - Oil Exporting (Box A-657)
  - Oil-Gas Prices (Box A-657)
  - Oil Import Program, 2 folders (Box A-657)
  - Ombudsman (Box A-658)
  - Opera Association, Connecticut (Box A-658)
  - Opticians, Commission (Box A-658)
  - Organizations, Regional and National (Box A-658)
  - Osteopathic Examination Board (Box A-658)
  - Out of State Travel, Vehicles (Box A-658)
  - Panuzio (Box A-658)
  - Parent Teacher’s Association of Connecticut (Box A-658)
  - Paris Peace Talks (Box A-658)
  - Parking Tickets (Box A-658)
  - Patriotism (Box A-658)
  - Pay Board, See Wage and Price Freeze (Box A-658)
  - Pension Report (Fed. Leg.) (Box A-658)
  - Pension Reform Bill – Federal Legislation (Box A-658)
  - Pension Study Committee – Request for Appointment (Box A-658)
  - Pensions (Box A-658)
  - Petroleum Control Commission (Box A-658)
  - Petroleum Products (Box A-658)
  - Petroleum Products Commission (Box A-658)
  - Pharmacist Letter (Box A-658)
  - Pharmacy Commission (Box A-658)
  - Pharmacy License (Box A-658)
  - Photographs (Box A-658)
  - Physical Therapists/Exam. Board (Box A-658)
  - Piping – Examining Board (Box A-658)
  - Plumbing: Also Board of Examiners (Box A-658)
  - Podiatrists (Box A-658)
  - Police, 2 folders (Box A-658)
  - Police Academy, Conn. (Box A-658)
  - Police (Box A-658)
    - Conn. Chief of Police Association (Box A-658)
    - In-Service Training Course (Box A-658)
    - Municipal Police Training Council (Box A-658)
    - Municipal Police Training Course – CT Police Academy, 2 folders (Box A-658)
    - New England Institute of Law Enforcement (Box A-658)
    - Quota System (Box A-658)
  - Political (Box A-658)
  - Political Process (Box A-658)
  - Political Programs (Box A-658)
  - Polls (Box A-658)
  - Population (Box A-658)
  - Pornography, 5 folders (Box A-659)
  - Power Shortage – OEP (Box A-659)
  - Post Office Department (Box A-659)
  - Postal Service – First Day Covers (Box A-659)
  - Postmaster General (Box A-659)
  - Poverty (Box A-659)
  - Power Facility Evaluation Council, 3 folders (Box A-659)
  - Power Facility Evaluation Council, 3 folders (Box A-660)
  - Power Failure (Box A-660)
  - Power Transmission Corridor – Petition (Box A-660)
  - Powercel (Box A-660)
  - Prayer Amendment (Box A-660)
  - Prayer Breakfasts (Box A-660)
  - Primaries (Box A-660)
  - Prisoners of War (Box A-660)
  - Proclamations – Arranged Alphabetically (Box A-660)
  - Proclamations – Correspondence (Box A-660)
  - Proclamations -- Correspondence, 3 folders (Box A-661)
  - Proclamations – General (Box A-661)
  - Proclamations – Special Proclamations – Special Session of the General Assembly (Box A-661)
  - Probate (Box A-661)
  - Psychiatrists (Box A-661)
  - Psychologists/Board of Examiners (Box A-661)
  - Public Concern (Box A-661)
  - Public Defender (Box A-661)
  - Public Expenditure Council, 4 folders (Box A-661)
  - Public Interest (Box A-661)
  - Publication (Box A-661)
  - Purchasing Division (Box A-661)
  - Questionnaire (Box A-662)
  - Questionnaire – National Organization (Box A-662)
  - Racism (Box A-662)
  - Radio Broadcasting – Federal Communications Commission (Box A-662)
  - Railroad Historical Association (Box A-662)
  - Real Estate Commission, 2 folders (Box A-662)
  - Real Estate Licensing (Box A-662)
  - Reale, Dante (Box A-662)
  - Reapportionment (Box A-662)
  - Recommendations (Box A-662)
  - Recommendations from TJM, 3 folders (Box A-662)
  - Red Cross Blood Program (Box A-662)
  - Redistricting (Box A-662)
  - Referendum (Box A-662)
  - Refineries (Box A-662)
  - Regional Councils (Box A-662)
  - Regional Planning Agencies (Box A-662)
  - Rehabilitation Dept. (Box A-662)
  - Religion (Box A-662)
  - Religious (Box A-662)
  - Rent Commission (Box A-662)
  - Repayments (Box A-662)
  - Republican Governor’s Association, 1 folder (Box A-662)
  - Republican Governors’ Association, 2 folders (Box A-663)
  - Republican Governors Campaign Committee (Box A-663)
  - Republican Governors Conference (Box A-663)
  - Republican National Committee, 2 folders (Box A-663)
  - Republican National Committee – Talking Papers (Box A-663)
  - Republican National Convention (Box A-663)
  - Republican Party (Box A-663)
  - Republican Platform, 1972 (Box A-663)
  - Republican State Central Committee, 2 folders (Box A-663)
  - Republican State Central Committee “Four Ten” (Box A-663)
  - Research Commission, 1 folder (Box A-663)
  - Research Commission, 1 folder (Box A-664)
  - Residence – Governor’s (Box A-664)